<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Everyday Kayla]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Everyday Kayla]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/everyday-kayla/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2015 04:03:42 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/everyday-kayla/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[About Kayla]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>About Kayla</h1><p>Kayla Styczinski B.S., University of Minnesota, is an apparel designer who focuses on designing garments that are simplistic, functional, and inspired. Kayla was able to study at the London College of Fashion; it was there that she was able to take classes such as shoemaking, advanced illustration, and leather accessories. Kayla also had the opportunity to work for Tara LaTour, a couture bridal design company based in Minnesota, as assistant designer and dressmaker. It is from these experiences that Kayla has found a strong attention to detail, a standard of quality, and an enthusiasm for the creative process. </p><img src="http://www.everydaykayla.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/01/KAYLA_2-300x200.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/everyday-kayla/about-kayla/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">30ff7466-b5c3-4843-879a-1e5d8700ef34</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2015 04:03:18 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[10 THINGS I LEARNED ON THE JOB]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>10 THINGS I LEARNED ON THE JOB</h1><p>A few weeks ago, I was introduced to a project TheLadders is running about lessons learned on your first jobs. TheLadders is a comprehensive career platform that helps make job searching simpler, focused, and more efficient! I encourage any of you who are on the job hunt tocheck them out! I remember around this time last year when I was going through the process of finding a job, scratch that, the NEVER ENDING process of finding a job (those of you who haven’t had to job hunt in these modern times when you are up against a TON of qualified candidates, you haven’t lived) All that being said, I wish I had discovered TheLadders while I was job hunting; every little bit helps!</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/everyday-kayla/10-things-i-learned-on-the-job/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">447868ca-c2f2-4c74-8767-9a180075341b</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2015 03:58:40 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>